dondengaeshi detatokoshoubu nerau wa ittou shou
An unexpected ending, deal with it as it comes,
we're aiming for first place
i can feel it donna toki datte hikari o shinjiteru
I Can Feel it, no matter what, I believe in the light
nigirishime ta yume ga koboreochi sou na
When the dream I've attained is
toki ni kagitte omoidasu no
about to fall apart, I remember
aitsu no ano yasashii kao
His kind expression,
mune no oku ga mata tsuyoku nareru no
the core of my heart is strengthened once again
bukkirabou no kokoro ni fire
My blunt mind is set ablaze,
gutto kuru ashita o tsukami tain da
I want to grasp tomorrow as it comes at me
mada mi nu sekai wa kowaku nai
I'm not afraid of the world I haven't seen,
shinji ta mirai desho hora let’s try!
isn't this the future we believed in? Come on Let's try!
kazoekire nai ano namida wa sou sa niji ni kawaru darou
Those countless tears, will they change into a rainbow?
osaekire nai kanashimi mo
That sorrow I can't contain
itsuka wa dakishime rareru ka na
Will I be able to embrace you someday?
yawa na haato ga uzukidashi tara
When my feeble heart begins to throb
arittake asu ni kisu shite ageyou
I give all of my kisses to tomorrow
furue ta mama no chiisana kobushi o tsuyoku mata nigitte
Still trembling, I clench my tiny fist tightly
dondengaeshi detatokoshoubu nerau wa ittou shou
An unexpected ending, deal with it as it comes,
we're aiming for first place
i can feel it donna toki datte hikari o shinjiteru
I Can Feel it, no matter what, I believe in the light
Killer Bee Rappuden: Part 2
(キラービー)アクロバット！
Acrobat!
少しはやるな… 人柱力。
So the Jinchuriki can fight,
a little.
なかなかやるが 仲よくなれぬ。
I can fight well, I'm infallible.
But to you, I can't be affable.
(ナルト)サスケの居場所
知ってんなら教えやがれ！
If you know where Sasuke is...
... tell me!
何!?
What?
(イタチ)サソリ！ デイダラ！
俺は ここまでにする。
Sasori! Deidara!
I'm done here.
(デイダラ)ここまでとは
どういう意味だ？
What do you mean, "I'm done"?
(イタチ)俺は 暁を抜ける。
I'm leaving the Akatsuki.
(デイダラ)あ～ん
何言ってやがんだ こら！
What are you saying?
(イタチ)俺は 長門とともに去る。
I'm leaving with Nagato.
あ～っ！ 逃げんな！
Don't run away!
おい！ どうする サソリの旦那？
Hey, so what are we going to do,
Sasori, my man?
どうもこうもない。
俺たちで そいつらを倒すだけだ。
Do you need to even ask?
We're going to
take them down ourselves!
(我愛羅)３対２だが。
It's three against two.
Doesn't matter.
関係ない。
まあ そういうことだな。
Guess you're right, hmm.
うん おいらの芸術を見せてやる。
I'll show them my art.
なんだ こりゃ？
(フウ)お前たち！
What is this?
Hey, you!
(フウ)
滝隠れの里で 何を騒いでいる！
Why are you causing an uproar
in the Hidden Waterfall Village?
なんだ あいつ？
Who is that?
(牛鬼)七尾の人柱力だ。
あいつが…。
That's the Seven Tails' Jinchuriki!
She is?
おい 重明！
Hey, Chomei!
(重明)フウ お仲間だ。
Fuu, they're comrades.
Comrades? Of mine?
仲間？ あっしの？
人柱力！ やつらが敵！
Hey, Jinchuriki!
They're the enemy!
I don't understand
what you're saying.
何言ってるか わかんないっす。
４対２だな。
引くぞ。
Now it's four against two.
Okay, let's retreat!
何!? よし。
What? Okay!
(デイダラ)お前ら 覚えてろよ！
I'll get you next time!
あっ！ 逃げやがった。
What? They took off!
(キラービー)滝隠れのフウだな。
You're Fuu of
the Hidden Waterfall, right?
♪♪「拳を合わせろ！」
Gimme a fist bump!
Hey, what's the matter?
おい どうした？
おじさん 胡散臭いっす。
You're kinda shady, mister.
何をいうか ベイビー。
What're you saying, baby?
C'mon, gimme a fist bump!
♪♪「拳を合わせろ！」
おい どうした？
Hey, what's the matter?!
おじさん 胡散臭いっす！
You're kinda shady, mister.
What're you saying, baby?
何をいうか ベイビー！ それ！
C'mon!
Gimme a fist bump!
♪♪「拳を合わせろ！」
嫌っす！
No!
– A fist bump!
– No!
拳を…。
嫌っす！
合わせろ！
– Give it here!
– No!
合わせろ！
嫌っす！
At any rate...
just give him a fist bump.
とにかく
拳を合わせてみるってばよ。
Gimme a fist bump!
♪♪「拳を合わせろ！」
嫌っす！
No!
ぶわ～!!
Wait! You have a mission
to carry out!
待て！ お前には
使命があるんだぞ！
他の里の忍の指図は
受けないっす！
I don't take orders from shinobi
from another village!
(我愛羅)俺たちは 仲間なんだ。
We're comrades.
You could even say we are friends.
あるいは
友と言ってもいいだろう。
Friends? We're friends?
友？ 友達？
そうだ。 お前は
１人なんかじゃない。
Yes. You are not alone.
Fuu seems to have
softened up to Gaara!
フウの姉ちゃん
我愛羅には懐いたぞ！
This started out
with a lot of trouble.
♪♪「展開に不服！ 結果に納得」
But I'll say,
the result is acceptable.
ビーのおっちゃん そのヒゲと
グラサンが悪いんだってばよ。
Octopops, I think your facial hair
and shades are to blame.
うるさい！ 次 いくぞ 次！
Shut up!
Let's move on to the next one!
十尾？ 何すか？ それ。
Ten Tails?
What's that?
暁が召喚した巨大兵器だ。
A gigantic weapon that
the Akatsuki summoned!
そいつが
尾獣のチャクラを吸い取ったせいで➡
It absorbed
the Tailed Beasts' chakra
みんな 全力が出せないでいる。
which is why we can't
utilize our full power.
今は 十尾のほうも
全力が出せない。
Right now, Ten Tails can't summon
its full power either.
落風城の姫が封じている。
The princess of Rappu Castle
sealed it.
だが 満月の夜
十尾の力が最大になる。
But the Ten Tails has ultimate power
on the night of the full moon.
They'll target the princess
and go to the castle.
やつらは 姫を狙って
城に攻めてくる。
Unless every Jinchuriki
comes together,
俺たち 人柱力が
すべて揃わなければ➡
we won't have a chance against it.
対抗できない。
９人で 姫と城を守るんだぜい。
The nine of us will protect
the princess and the castle... yay.
イェイ！
♪♪「拳を合わせろ！」
Gimme a fist bump.
W-What's the big idea?
い… いきなり 何するってばよ！
(九喇嘛)おい 孫悟空！ 俺たちは
敵じゃねえって そいつに伝えな。
Hey, Son Goku!
Tell him that we're not enemies!
(孫悟空)だとよ。
You heard him.
(老紫)これはすまぬ。
I'm sorry about that.
近ごろ 怪しい者どもが
現れるようになってな。
Suspicious characters
have been showing up lately.
てっきり その一味かと。
So I assumed you were one of them.
やっぱり！ そのヒゲとグラサンが
悪いんだってばよ！
I'm telling you...
it's that facial hair and shades.
No need to critique my physique.
♪♪「俺の美学 ご意見いらぬ」
怪しい者どもとは？
What do you mean by
"suspicious characters"?
正体は わからぬ。
I don't know who they are...
だが 村の子供を
さらっていくのだ。
but they've been kidnapping
children from our village.
確かに 獲物を狙う風情だな。
It definitely appears like
it's tracking prey...
重明 追っ払ってくるっす！
Chomei!
Let's chase 'em away!
承知。
Agreed.
Scale Powder!
麟粉！
あっ！
口寄せか？
It was a summoning?
If you interfere,
I'll show you no mercy.
(サスケ)
邪魔立てすれば容赦はしない。
あっ！ サスケ。
Sasuke!
ナルト お前 里を出られたのか？
Naruto...
You were able to leave the village?
お前こそ 木ノ葉の里に
帰るってばよ。
What about you?
You're coming back to the village!
お前の指図は受けない。
I don't take orders from you!
人さらいはお前の仕業か！
Are you the kidnapper?!
それがどうした？
What of it?
サスケ お前 大蛇丸の手下に
成り下がって➡
Sasuke! You've stooped so low
to be Orochimaru's underling,
こんなことやってんのかよ。
that you've started
doing things like this?
And you don't even know
how Itachi's feels!
イタチの気も知らねえでよ。
Don't you dare mention
Itachi's name!
お前がイタチを語るな！
イタチは暁を抜けて
お前を捜してんだぞ！
Itachi deserted the Akatsuki
and is looking for you!
なに!?
What?
My, my...
(大蛇丸)おやおや
人柱力がお揃いで➡
A gathering of Jinchuriki...
I wonder what
you're all planning to do?
何をしようってのかしら。
Orochimaru...
大蛇丸…。
Although you're probably helpless
もっとも 尾獣の力のほとんどが
奪われている状態で➡
because your Tailed Beast powers
have been stolen...
何もできやしないでしょうけど。
サスケ君
やっつけてしまいましょうか。
Sasuke... Shall we destroy them?
Orochimaru... I'm done here.
大蛇丸 俺はここまでにする。
What? What do you mean
"I'm done"?
えっ？ ここまでとは
どういうこと？
俺はイタチを追う。
I'm going after Itachi.
あっ！ 待てよ！
ナルト！ 使命を忘れるな！
Hey, hold it!
Naruto!
Don't forget the mission at hand!
人さらいの元凶め！
貴様はここで成敗してくれる！
You're the one
behind the kidnappings!
I'll punish you now!
Powerless Jinchuriki...
力足らずの人柱力が
大きな口をたたかないことね。
I wouldn't talk if I were you...
口寄せの術！
Summoning Jutsu!
So, what are you going to do?
さあ どうするのかしら？ フフフ…。
Son Goku!
孫悟空！
うぉ～！
Lord Orochimaru!
大蛇丸様！
大丈夫よ。
I'm okay!
うぅ… チャクラが切れやがった。
I'm out of chakra...
Shukaku!
守鶴！
(守鶴)うぉ～！
大蛇丸様！
大丈夫。
Lord Orochimaru!
I'm okay!
(フウ)行くっす！
My turn!
Lord Orochimaru!
大蛇丸様！
大丈夫。
I'm okay...
Tailed Beast Lariat!
(キラービー)尾獣ラリアット！
L-Lord Orochimaru!
おぉ 大蛇丸様！
あら 食らいすぎ。
Oh my... This is too much
even for me.
Take this!
食らいやがれ！
どうだ？
やった！
– Well?!
– We did it!
No, that's just shed skin.
いや 抜け殻だ。
Even if they're weakened,
力不足の尾獣でも➡
they still pack a punch
when they join forces.
数を揃えれば
そこそこやるようね。
He's as tough as ever.
さすがにしぶとい。
でも ヘロヘロしてるっす。
But he looks worn out!
大蛇丸様。
覚えてらっしゃい。
Lord Orochimaru...
I'll get you next time!
One down...
１つ片づいたな。
暁の陰謀を阻止するために➡
Come with us so that we can
put a stop to the Akatsuki's plot.
一緒に来てくれ。
うむ。
よし… ユギトたちと合流する。
All right.
We'll join up with Yugito
and the others.
(ユギト)三尾の人柱力 やぐらが
まだ見つからないの。
I still can't locate Yagura,
the Three Tails' Jinchuriki.
He wasn't in the Land of Water.
(ユギト)水の国にはいなかったわ。
Any clues?
(キラービー)手がかりは？
どこかの湖のほとり。
Yagura is supposedly heading to
some wetlands somewhere...
そこに やぐらが
向かったというのだけど➡
確証はないわ。
But I can't verify it.
Even if you can't, we need
all of the Jinchuriki, right?
確証がなくたって 人柱力全員が
揃わなきゃならねえんだろ？
そうだ。
すべての尾獣が揃わなければ➡
Yeah, unless every Jinchuriki
comes together,
we can't beat the Ten Tails!
十尾には勝てない。
やつらは 次の満月に➡
Those guys will begin their attack
on the next full moon...
攻撃をかけてくる。
封印が弱まるときを狙って。
targeting the time when
the seal will weaken.
How much time do we have left?
あと どれくらいだ？
(ユギト)７日ほどね。
About seven days.
Let's split up and
search for Yagura.
手分けして
やぐらを見つけるのよ。
Otherwise,
でなければ １人欠けたままで
暁と決戦になるのか。
we'll have to fight the Akatsuki
with one member short?
We'll split up into two-man teams
and search in all four directions.
(キラービー)ツーマンセルで 四方に散るぜ。
いいか みんな！
結果はともあれ➡
All right, everyone!
No matter what the result,
do not fail to gather at
Rappu Castle in seven days!
７日後には
必ず落風城に集合しろ。
行くぜ ユギト！
Let's go, Yugito!
うん？
Look forward to working with you.
Okay...
(ハン)よろしくだで。
オーケー。
Can you see anything?
No...
There's mist everywhere.
なんか見えるか？
いや 霧ばかりだ。
Then I'll check around in Sage Mode.
う～ん んじゃ
仙人モードで感知してみっか。
What's that?!
What's wrong?
ん？ なんだ？
(我愛羅)どうした？
Pursuers from the Leaf...
木ノ葉の追っ手だ。
俺を捜してるんだ。
They're looking for me!
Get on!
乗れ。
It seems no one wants to give
Jinchuriki their freedom.
どこも人柱力を 自由に
させておきたくないようだな。
Yeah...
They treat us like dangerous vessels
that contain Tailed Beasts.
ああ。
まるで尾獣の入った
危険な入れ物扱いだ。
We're not dangerous,
and neither are Tailed Beasts!
尾獣も俺たちも
危険なんかじゃねえってばよ。
It's Yagura,
the Three Tails' Jinchuriki.
(ハン)三尾の人柱力 やぐらだな。
Gimme a fist bump.
♪♪「拳を合わせろ！」
I refuse.
(やぐら)嫌だ。
Isobu, tell him!
磯撫 そいつに伝えてくれ。
Without a doubt,
these two look suspicious,
確かにこの２人
見た目は怪しいが➡
but they are Jinchuriki friends.
人柱力の仲間なんだとな。
Jinchuriki don't have friends.
(やぐら)
人柱力に仲間なんかいない。
Just being Jinchuriki fills people
with fear, resentment and hatred.
俺たちは 人柱力というだけで
人に恐れられ➡
憎まれ いみ嫌われる。
Sometimes, we're hunted by
people of our own village.
時に同じ里の者に命を狙われる。
That's our fate as Jinchuriki!
それが人柱力の運命だ。
So I want no part of this.
I'll stay here by myself.
そんなのはまっぴらだから
俺は１人でここにいる。
We need your power.
お前の力が必要だ。
Go away!
Come with us.
That is your destiny.
帰れ。
一緒に来い それがお前の運命だ。
Don't force anymore destiny on me.
俺にこれ以上の運命を強要するな。
Do you want me to force him?
力ずくか。
Stay out of this.
お前は手を出すな。
We are all Jinchuriki.
俺たちは 同じ人柱力だ。
The fate forced on me as a Jinchuriki
is more than enough for me!
人柱力という運命を➡
背負わせられただけで
もうたくさんだ！
Whether it was forced on you or not,
this is your fate!
背負わされたんだろうが
なんだろうが➡
そいつがお前の運命なんだよ！
うるさい！
Shut up!
Fool, ya fool...
バカ野郎 この野郎。
As long as it's your destiny,
you've got to see it through!
背負った以上は その運命を
貫くしかねえだろう！
うお～！
Bee?!
ビー。
You!
We're the same Jinchuriki as you.
(やぐら)お前…。
俺たちは 同じ人柱力。
We don't fear you.
We don't resent you.
恐れない 憎まない 嫌わない。
And we don't hate you.
Gimme a fist bump.
♪♪「拳を合わせろ！」
Let's combine your power
with ours.
(キラービー)お前の力を
俺たちと合わせてくれ。
It will soon be the night
of the full moon.
(ウタカタ)間もなく満月の夜になる。
How come Octopops isn't here?
He's the one who planned all of this.
なんで 言い出しっぺのビーの
おっちゃんたちが来ねえんだよ。
Not just one person is missing,
but three.
１人欠けるどころか
３人も欠けるとは。
Will we be able to pull this off?
これで なんとかなるっすか？
Probably not.
ならないだろうな。
What should we do, Aunty Yugito?
どうすんだよ？ ユギトのおばちゃん。
おばちゃん？
"Aunty"?
Oh, I mean... Sister Yugito.
あ？ いや… ユギトのお姉さん。
We have no choice but to have faith
that Bee and the others will come.
ビーたちが必ず来ると信じて
持ちこたえるしかない。
They've appeared.
現れたぞ。
お？
Go!
ゆけ！
(みんな)おぉ～！
Let's go too, hmm.
俺たちも行こうぜ うん！
No need to rush.
Wait for the moon to rise.
慌てることはない。
月の出るのを待て。
(みんな)わぁ～！
The Akatsuki genin are attacking!
暁の下忍どもが来るっす！
Defend the castle!
Don't let a single one get inside!
防ぐよ 城内へ一歩も入れるな！
(みんな)わぁ～！
Water Style: Bubble Jutsu!
水遁 泡沫の術！
Lava Style: Scorching Rocks Jutsu!
溶遁 灼河流岩の術！
Wind Style: Rasen Shuriken!
風遁 螺旋手裏剣！
(我愛羅)ハァ～！
Looks like we have to
get involved, hmm?
やっぱり俺たちが出ないとダメだろ。
うん！
That's not necessary.
それには及ばない。
The Gedo Statue?!
They're gonna use that to attack!
外道魔像！
あれで攻撃するつもりっすよ。
It won't be at full strength,
but it should suffice.
全力とはいかないが
これでも十分だろ。
But there isn't a single fragment
of art to it though.
芸術性は カケラもねえけどな。
It's a Tailed Beast Bomb!
(ウタカタ)尾獣玉！
Damn! The way I am right now,
I can't take it down.
クソ！ 今のわしらには
撃てねえってのに！
Is everyone okay?
みんな 大丈夫か!?
Now! Charge!
今だ！ かかれ！
(みんな)わ～！
Th-This isn't good!
Steam Dash!
ま まずいっす！
(ハン)蒸気驀進！
でや～！
That's...!
Friends!
あれは！
仲間たちよ！
Now that I'm here,
you don't have to worry!
この俺が来たからには
もう大丈夫だ！
Sorry to keep you waiting!
待たせたな。
おっせえよ！ ビーのおっちゃん！
You're late, Octopops!
But you found Yagura of the Three Tails!
でも 三尾のやぐらを
見つけたのね！
Yeah! All nine of us are together!
おう！ これで９人 揃ったぞ！
Okay, Jinchuriki!
さあ 人柱力たち！
Raise your fists!
拳を突き上げろ！
(みんな)お～！
What is that?!
なんだありゃ!?
One Tail.
Two Tails.
Three Tails.
一尾。
二尾！
Four Tails.
Five Tails.
三尾！
四尾。
Six Tails.
Seven Tails.
五尾。
六尾。
Eight Tails.
七尾っす！
八尾。
And Nine Tails, y'know!
九尾だってばよ！
We are the Jinchuriki
who stand before you!
俺たち人柱力！ 今ここに立つ！
That's kind of artsy!
う… なんかあれ… 芸術っぽいぞ。
It doesn't matter at this point
if they're assembled together.
今更 ９人揃おうが無駄だ。
(みんな)はっ！
Hey, hey...
There are Tailed Beast Bombs
over there too.
おいおい 向こうも尾獣玉だ。
それがどうした。
What of it?
Shukaku!
Matatabi!
Isobu!
(我愛羅)守鶴！
(ユギト)又旅！
Son Goku!
(やぐら)磯撫！
(老紫)孫悟空！
Kokuo!
Saiken!
Chomei!
(ハン)穆王！
(ウタカタ)犀犬！
Gyuki!
(フウ)重明！
(キラービー)牛鬼！
Kurama!
九喇嘛！
This isn't good!
おわっ！ やべえ！
Don't think you've won!
これで勝ったと思うなよ！
Next time,
I swear you're going down! Hmm!
次は ぜってえ倒してやるぜ！
うん！
Phew...
I'm pooped.
ふう しんでえな。
I'm out of chakra again.
また チャクラ切れだぜ。
We won.
勝ったわね。
We did it!
Yeah, we did.
やったぜ。
ああ だが➡
But unless we get back
our Tailed Beast power,
尾獣の力を取り戻さないかぎり➡
we can't call this a true victory.
真の勝利とはいえないぜ。
That said...
Today's a huge win!
もっとも…。
今日のところは大勝利！
ハハハハ！
フフフ…。
(キラービー)フフフ。
terase asu wo ima kokoro tsutau messeeji
Shine a light, tomorrow is now,
a message straight to the heart
boku to yoku ni ta itami uchiake te kure ta hito
Hearing someone tell me about
the same kind of pain I have
futo hitori ja nain datte omoetan da
Made me think that I'm not alone
dakedo nagareta namida kamishime ta nukumori o
But the flowing tears and the warmth I relished
itsumade mo boku wa dakishimete ireru ka na?
How long can those envelop me?
kizutsui te kizutsui te nai te nai te tsuyoku nare subete
Hurting again and again,
crying over and over gives you strength for everything
me ni utsuru sono keshiki wa eien ni tada kokoro e to
That scenery you see goes straight to the heart,
massugu tsunagatte iku
now and forever
hanate niji no sora omoi nara koko ni aru (my heart)
Let it go, the rainbow sky, my wishes are here (My heart)
terase asu wo ima kokoro tsutau messeeji
Shine a light, tomorrow is now,
a message straight to the heart
hanate niji no sora
Let it go, the rainbow sky
Karin! Wake up!
Karin! Get a hold of yourself!
すごい人で。
もう 皆さん すばらしい。
I'll go get the Medical unit now!
あったかいですなぁ。
あったかいですね。
今日も 張り切っていこう。
はい。
Sasuke, Sasuke, it's okay...
北島先生に
お願いがあるんですけども。
お願い？
はい。
お金なら…。
It's too—
ないよ？
So... so... I have a request...
北島先生の 『風雪ながれ旅』を➡
ご一緒させて
いただけないでしょうか。
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"To See That Smile,
Just One More Time."
氷川さん。
はい。
Like that one time, back then...
よろしくお願いします。
よろしくお願いします！
やった～！
やりましょう！